Derrick Igoe

Neenah, WI 54956 digoe87@gmail.com +1 920 470 1408

I have a very big passion for Technology. Figuring out issues and resolving anything that revolved around computers or technology in general is very fascinating. I have a big passion for learning continuously and personally feel that the best way to strive for success is to never be satisfied. Always push higher and for better results.

I have multiple references, and I am more than willing to provide them upon request.

Projects I have worked on:

At PBL, I was also instrumental in the design and implementation of the website for our lab division, parsonsbehlelab.com. I was also responsible for maintenance on the website and changing text here and there to keep it up-to-date.

Also at PBL, I have worked fixing smaller bugs and technical issues in regards to the Automation platform we developed that allowed users to put in preset information and edit at will. Then it would allow them to automatically create documents that will comply with GDPR, CCPA and HIPAA policies.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Consumer Service Representative

Alta Resources - Neenah, WI February 2022 to Present

Take inbound phone calls and solve consumer problems.

- Solve Consumer problems related to Direct to Consumer products
- Work with team in a environment that is conducive to handle inbound phone calls, emails and social media posts.

Crew Member

McDonalds - Appleton, WI November 2018 to February 2022

My job was to help customers and provide great customer service, ranging from accurate order taking to fast efficient and friendly service.

AMXL - **Driver**

Amazon DSP - Neenah, WI February 2021 to November 2021

Regularly drove 16' and 26' trucks to deliver packages averaging 75 lbs or up to 300 lbs.

Sales Representative

Salelytics - Appleton, WI July 2020 to February 2021

My job is B2B selling and helping customers shipping needs. I am currently on the FedEx team, and I call businesses to discuss shipping needs and to seek to reduce bottom line cost for shipping. I manage the businesses account information in a system called Salesforce. I regularly make calls, check shipping needs, enter the necessary information and then move on to the next client.

Software Developer

Parsons Behle & Latimer Lab - Salt Lake City, UT March 2018 to November 2018

Worked as part of a team in developing a cutting edge law automation platform. I worked on several tasks regarding the usage of HTML5, CSS, and JS in a Vue framework.

General Manager (GM)

A&W Restaurants - Appleton, WI May 2013 to April 2018

Lead a team in order to promote sales growth and team unity. As a GM my duties included but were definitely not limited to, maintaining a positive sales increase from week to week, doing scheduling and shift planning, balancing books to make sure all the money was accounted for, and employee wellness and happiness. From time to time I did some repair work on machines we use in the store with a little help from google.

Delivery Manager

Papa John's - Appleton, WI June 2012 to May 2014

My job was to manager delivery drivers to send them out to specific routes in accordance to time restraint and a first-come first-serve basis. Planning and managing routes as well as helping in-store make pizza's to running the store.

Education

High school or equivalent

Skills

- HTML 5
- CSS
- Javascript
- Git
- Software Development
- GitHub